Yeah. Anyway, there you go. I'll let you take back over.
DIRECTOR HERSEY- All right. DIRECTOR DEWOLF- Master Day Scrum. DIRECTOR MACK PELOSI Organize that.
all righty
DIRECTOR HAMPSON- So first we have Dan with this 2-1-4-7-6
I think we're getting close to getting this off our plate and into stage for you.
He just sent another note to that group, Andrew.
Chelsea, Amy from marketplace and said, you know, I asked him last night.
have any objections to this and cricket so far. So I sent him another note because Rob's ready to go ahead.
push this change and a few other changes and then we'll do a UAT.
in on residential probably, you know.
I don't know if they're working or what they're doing next week, and then we'll get this moved to Pratt.
So there's a few more that are like that. So when we get to those, I'll just say, yep.
part of the residential push. Okay. Easy peasy. Christy.
1-2-9-2-3-4
No new update.
All right. Same on the next one. There's no new update on that.
one. ELLIE WILSON- All righty. Dan. DAN BALZ- Yeah it's just
It's in the queue. All right. Aaron.
store true ice I know you didn't
DIRECTOR MACKAY I'll update on that. Yeah. DIRECTOR MACKAY Okay. DIRECTOR MACKAY We've not made any progress on that.
I think Lawrence was going to handle next steps for that.
Undertexter av Nicolai Winther
All righty. Dan, 2023.
penetration test. Yeah I put the update in there. Still.
three of 22 resolved and in pride um there's going to be four
changes going out and I have to confirm looks like purpose.
fix the four items that they had for international. So hopefully.
That number will drop or go to the upper number will go to.
11 in the coming weeks.
perhaps it'll go to seven as soon as today depending on if they deployed those to
i think they did that's the thing i got but i'm just gonna go check something and yeah
So moving along. Awesome.
Next one, Erin, Megan.
I have the calculator up for this.
built out and looking nice. I'm working on the actual recommendations, the actual
calculations of it.
I know I've been working on the calculator for a bit, but... Yeah, I haven't done it.
anything so would this update still be correct then built out
later outline yeah i think it's probably more than 20 but okay
Do you want me just to push it to 30 or 40?
be okay with saying 30. yeah
Ready?
Next one we got is Dan, eStore Review and Purge.
Yeah, I have the solution. They actually have something in there.
where you can have it show that your account's been disabled.
And so that way, if somebody would come back with an old account.
that's been not used for several years, they would get a message as opposed to just it.
go with erroring out i also found out what other login statuses do so it's good exercise
I know what I need to do. And now the work to get.
the logistics to get it moved into stage, execute the script and stage, test and...
stage do the script and proud all that the logistics are going to take longer
it's going to take to fix the issue but there you go i'll get that
going when I can. We got one outstanding item on this next one.
There's been some back and forth. There's a resource that's in Azure.
that apparently nobody has access to. Shanks, Patricia, David.
Andy I mean God I don't know so
Apparently, apparently this.
This vaulted resource is, yeah, nobody can.
access it so we don't know if there's anything in it so that's the last thing we want to delete before we call this done
and I don't know what the next steps are because like I just said all those people
don't have can't get into it to see what we would be deleting
So I'll look to David Alton to give me advice on that.
Yeah, that's true.
That is true. I'll ask if that's what they want to do.
All right, Christy.
So we just met on this.
I noticed that you had put in this. Are you thinking we should put this on hold? I thought they're going to.
to be working on it. Now, this is the one. This is the one.
one that nor I don't know how much work
Well, Aaron, what is your thought? Based on our conversation the other day, this is the one where NORS…
in those new fields and this is going to be the new parts inquiry and
I think there's going to be a lot more to do with this because there's more.
things than just those fields that are going to need to point to E1.
If this is the same application we're talking about doing that feature flag yesterday, we have to...
make sure that the data sources are all right.
to add, I guess it's not that much, but it's not as done as nor thinks.
it is, I think. Okay, because I thought we were a little close.
closer to but I guess you're right especially we're going to piggyback off of this
ticket for the feature flag or the other ticket because the other ticket is for e1 and
I kind of thought that's what David was saying. The original part.
arts inquiry because this isn't a branch right on on in uh
source control so uh we did branch it but yeah it's going to be so
application so the other will merge application
The other application for E1 is the one that we've got to.
focus on the feature flag for, I thought, because that we.
David wants it so it works in E1 and it works in world and we can just flip that flag.
So I was thinking that flag would be over there. Then do we want another flag?
for this one where we have the new fields present. No, no, so there's only...
one applic there isn't another application there's only one right so originally
I thought we were going to have like an E1 version and a world version, but that's not, that's not.
what Dave wants it and I guess this is how we're how we're handling it which makes sense
Because when he said it has to be deployed to hundreds of machines, yeah, you don't want to.
redeploy all those MSIs all at the same time along with everything else.
So this has to be a flag in like...
the configuration that we can just update a configuration file.
right but there's two things at play here right
There's the original parts. There's a table, Zach, saying. So, no, so we are changing.
the original parts inquiry, like we're updating that to contain all of the features.
for E1 that will be activated with a feature flag.
talk about it offline but basically there there's more to do with this one
Yeah, I mean, there's this one and there's the other ticket, Christy. So I don't know which ticket.
we want to bury this or, you know, leverage that feature.
It needs to be on this one. I think so too, because it is.
because the other one is really for CRP and we want to just put that to the side and say this is ready for.
CRP. And then this one is where we do all the real work on.
and getting it prepared. I got you. I got you. Okay.
That's fine. Yeah, then somebody can remove that comment if you want.
I thought since we weren't deploying this for several months
to put it on hold. Since we're not going to.
deploy this until we clean the data. Well, no, I think we are going to.
I think we're, so the idea is that it's a feature flag. So we just leave the new.
fields off until we switch to E1 or we're ready to bring it in.
Or maybe we have two feature flags, one for, well, we'll talk about it, but I think the
of this is totally independent of the data cleanup effort. If I was understanding Dave correctly.
Exactly. Christy, is that what you got too?
Yeah, I think what the plan was is to hide those fields, to go ahead and have them there.
but hide them yeah until he won yeah but that way we can just turn them back on
on when we're ready. We don't have to redeploy.
And I guess it probably will have, well, who knows how long the data cleanup effort will take.
be yeah i thought a long time personally but okay
all good yeah all righty the next one we got is for
Erin.
I kind of put this one on hold because the ice calculator was more important.
probably start this one well I started it
I'll probably come back to this either tomorrow or...
after New Year's. Okay.
All right. Oops. Our next one is Dan.
the add to residential. DIRECTOR HERSEY- Yeah that's.
going to be done next year. It's kind of interesting. I went through every ticket.
that I had open yesterday and I for some reason these weren't showing up
the two there's been two so far because i put updates on like 20 tickets yesterday
I have that issue sometimes too. Okay. I don't know what I did wrong.
Well, here's another one, Cloudflare Enterprise.
Yeah, that's frustrating. No, no update on it.
same same update as what was in there before so you can just change the date if you want
Easy peasy. All right. Our next one is for.
Christy, Creatability for Users. Yeah, there's no update on that.
this one right now. Awesome sauce. Next one, Dan.
Yeah, we're going back and forth.
one has an accurate update we're going back and forth with shopify support and they're not getting it
So I don't know. But yeah, they need to help.
us understand what we need to do to get validated so we can get to the next step so this
Just slow going, but it is what it is.
All right. Megan anything on this one.
no i mean it's going okay cool
Do you want to go over any of these Dan the pen test.
No, she can just buzz past.
Pentest Residential. DIRECTOR HERSEY- No I'll get those updated after.
Rob does this thing. Okay.
international ones are in here too so yeah i'll get those updated according
and probably get them moved into either in Pratt or to UH.
once we get them deployed to stage.
Okay. Anything on the e-store? Well...
Yeah, just leave it where it's at. I'm using that ticket to document the...
process for basically for customers and discounts
since that was an issue. Anyway, it's fine.
Aaron, IT Wiki. I've not.
started on it okay catalog domains Dan
Yes, I got those all.
cataloged. I need to do a little cleanup on that.
So why, I wonder why this is, what status is this in?
You probably have it in the wrong. Yep.
So. Okay.
General software custom. Okay, I need to remember to do that because I created this just yet.
Is this marketing, technically? No, this is completely...
IT related. So I would put it under IT. Yeah. Business solutions.
Yeah. Oops. Okay. Yeah.
the request templates too recently.
It has some information in it. Okay.
Megan mobile menu and main menu do not match.
Yeah, I fixed that. I'll close it. Okay.
And then our last one, Dan, B2B Migration Project.
yeah this is um just getting started
so I think Megan might have put this in there just uh as I did uh
placeholder for our integration so um
Aaron, you know, we'll talk more about this in the new year, but we probably.
we get together and start kind of mapping this out a little bit.
Now that we've made the decision to go with two stores.
This integration will get a little bit more. It's not that big of a deal, but a little.
hey, got to check for two flags, and then you'll know your destination based on the.
value of the flags that are in parts of the inquiry
I guess that's the other thing, Megan. We probably.
need to either resurrect or create a new ticket that says we need another feature
flag or that future flag another flag in parts of quarry to indicate whether
the part as a B to C. And so that's just one more checkbox.
the field so it'll be a database update and then add that check box and then based on the
value of those check boxes will integrate. And then there's some research.
should do and the api and things like that so this will probably get a little momentum starting
next year but for right now Aaron you've got so many other big priorities I just stay focused.
on them. Yeah, I'll schedule something for when we come back.
But I was thinking, Dan, I don't even know if you want to add the B to C flag.
because pricing is not correct in parts inquiry.
We can talk about that more, but. Yay. Yeah.
Because we wouldn't want to auto-upload the new part and then have the pricing be wrong.
be like uploading to draft status and then i could go in and
change it i don't know anyways i gotcha yeah let's i woke up at three
last night and all these sloshes came in my head and I wrote them down on my phone.
You're like a comedian who wakes up in the middle of the night and has the best jokes.
yeah great all right we're good but yeah i'll schedule something
for all of us to get back. Who should be involved in that? I don't want to waste.
David Alton's time, but do we need him in that discussion?
Let's just do it there. And Aaron, you're comfortable, right? And then we'll report back to David. You know, keep in mind.
update on it. That way calendars will be easier to find time on.
are you okay with that talking about the api and stuff you're you're gonna be the
SME I think for that so we'll just keep David in the loop
loop on our decision. I think everybody, and he is an uncomfortable elite.
moving towards the SSIS route and building it.
So, and then also just an FYI, Megan, another conversation.
we had. So for new integrations, we're talking about.
and SSIS and David's comfortable with that, I think. And then the order.
stuff. I think we're going to stick with Jitterbit for now, since it's up and working.
There's no sense in building that at this point.
If we decide to move off of Jitterbent in the future, then maybe something else. But with everything that.
David Strickland has done so far to make that thing work. I'd hate to.
abandon it. But there's some...
Fun stuff for Aaron lies ahead as far as building up integration to.
get customers and parts over so totally fine
Yippee. Alrighty.
Cool cats. I'll see you in a bit. Thank you. Bye. See y'all later. Bye.
Thank you.