Okay, here in the fire we gotta talk candlesticks. I know if you're
You've been trading for a while you're like, oh yeah, I'm just gonna skip over this one. Don't skip over it
important. And just a brief little recap. We have a high price. We have the open prices.
where it's gonna open, you have clothes, and you have a low price. And this right here.
this is where all the trades are placed. It's like, that's where all the
Actions act and as you know breaking news, I actually that that's just the
It's green, but all my candles I change them white and gray.
want to see where's the action happening. Now on the bit corn, which I traded.
with you, which is a terrible example to use, but a great example at the same time.
I will I will show you and there's something that you don't see so I'm gonna
at it. Right here is the top, that is the tippy top of the wick.
Again, I make my wicks real light. I can see them probably not good for f...
filming, that's actually the bottom. So there was so much
Well, not not a lot, but enough to take out your order. Because let's see you-
take out an order here and you're like, okay, we're gonna short this thing. And then you put in a stop.
Let's just say, oh, you know, let's go, let's go right there.
It gets taken out and you lose your money. If I were to measure this, let's start it.
the top and go to the bottom over here.
It's a seven over seven percent in a daily move.
And on exchanges, people know where the stops are and they're like, okay, let's
put in a lot of money and take all those out and then zinc so depending on the trade a lot of times
I don't use stops now don't listen to me, but I know with volatility and when it gets
taken out enough time, you're just like, okay, we're done. But look at the amount of...
action. Right? Nothing. That's nothing. But look, it edits...
almost a seven and a half percent move. And sometimes now this is crypto exchanges.
You're they'll they'll be down for maintenance and you'll have your stops ready and just you come back and
Everything's gone, it's just zinc, zinc. You would never think in an hour it would move 10th.
$1,000. So just be aware if you're trading crypto in futures.
volatility off the chart, so just plan accordingly. Because you-
You're gonna have a perfect setup. Let's say a falling wedge. You put your bio-
order there. And then in five minutes, it's just like zinc zinc. Then you go back and you look
your account because the following wedge plays out right it goes it goes all the way up there you're like
Yeah, wait a minute. So I'm just putting that out there when it comes to-
crypto, be careful. Or when it comes to stocks that have
very little volume. Also known as penny stocks or whatever. Your trading likes.
Spire, DIA, or the cues, there's not that kind of movement. I mean, it's not that they're...
can't be. It would just take a lot of volumes and a lot of humans and with that one I will see you in the-
next trade.