Oh, wait. The way you left yesterday, I was dealing with a fallout from that for the rest of the fucking day. He's 12. He doesn't, I mean, he doesn't need to be thinking he's a pain in your ass all the fucking time. And he doesn't need to be thinking about how life sucks than you die. And I'm sorry you felt bad. I'm going to do feel bad for you, but I mean, God.
is the rectus whole fucking. I don't know how to do it with you, but I'm sorry, you can't try me out the wall. Two, you know, it's that woman who's before the charade, but but it's like explaining to him, he wakes me up in the middle of the night all the time. He constantly, it's constantly depression. I don't know what fucking duty I feel like shit, I'm work on that, I'm about to go over such.
pressure on me like like now we have no insurance. I don't know if it's my fault I need to go get the full-time job I don't I don't fucking know. I mean it's like it's not anybody's fault. It's it's my mind You know I don't know I mean like it's it's just a problem So, it's a message clear Clear instructions and everything and then And then what what what's so so flattened it's like but but but but but but it's
It's just like, yeah, it's, I'm, I'm, no, it's not current. I don't know how to explain to you anything in the, I, I am sorry about how, how, what I've said yesterday it wasn't about anybody, it wasn't about how, it seems like we work, work, work, work, work, work, work, work, work, work, and what's going to happen. How do money is going away, you know, like if it's going to be nothing left of it because it's a fucking cow.
how inflation is going and insurance and everything and then just like I'm gonna look insurance now. Doctor and a doctor nobody's work hard if any problem out except what's the queue or or like everybody's trying like we're all here from people like I'm sorry I'll shut out here.
I'm not making any sense. Well, he can't be left to interpret that shit, you know? He can't be, he can't be. That is for sure. That shouldn't be on your shoulders. I mean, you want to complain about some behavior or something, that's one thing. You want to say something to him about a behavior, that's one thing. But just like me, on him. I'm telling you, my God. You are.
Michael makes some breakfast burritos for everybody, okay? And now I'm gonna figure out insurance. Now I'll be back. Do you want to eat special in your breakfast burrito? Let me know.
Okay. We're done. We need to try and get a little more strength. Yeah.
What else we got here? Oh, I'm not sure. Alright. What the fuck is that? It's got flying lines. What else we got there?
Ich habe hier auch eine Zahle, die ich schiebe.
煮た符 맘バターauze煮草
I'm going to go to the living room and come to the living room and push down. Work, work, work, work, work, work, work. How much work I could add to it like in the beginning where I am sour. And then people still like fucking push it down. Whether I like to wake up, you know, yeah.
You know, I'm fucking sorry that my mouth is not like I'm not like running around. You know, I see people cook, he's 23 pounds running around. It was better than I am. You know, I was so, so it is defeating me. I took it back. And you think you may, you start making more money. It's still like fucking getting mother-in-law's playing. Like, look how, what, what I need and I want to know what I don't need and how.
She... you have such a nice husband she... he loves you. I was really scared by the money. What? Who says that? You didn't told me he allows you to spare the money. You know, and maybe she was tossing it off. You were just talking about her fucking self dead. You... God. Who says the wind that she's in? It wasn't about the kitchen. Kitchen.
It hasn't been respected. No, that's a pun. That's fine. That's fine. It's not there. It's just like you're at 430, but it's fine. I think that's what's so easy. Oh, I think that's what's happened the other day. I got up. I knew that that was going to be about the state of the house. So instead of working for Malibu, I couldn't help you.
I want to work today, you know, to make up. I'm just gonna get some fucking cops. I'm just gonna get some fucking cops. Tell him you fucking do so. Say, you know what you're right. How about you have this cleaned up by the time I get home? You can't see me. Oh my god. Look at this. There's...
It goes like, oh, okay, you know what I feel over the world. Well, everybody needs a cave and that's what I'm going to record. I'm going to go look at me, you know, like, oh, fucking look at you. If you can handle it, that's great. Everything whoever tells me like, hey, you know what? I don't see it. You're really young. You're so hot, like, oh.
I'm just hearing the people's ears sometimes. Like, you need to have your head used to go to the doctor or whatever, like, I mean, no, no, no, like, because then bring out your fucking supporter who has a voice. Well, I'll tell you what, those people have a voice because they don't fuck. They never come off. They get it. And continue doing.
I'm just gonna stop and hold the door and then we go. Get down the stairs. Should go for the right. Okay, just keep moving. Just keep moving. I think I'm holding you. Hmm? I think I'm holding you. Catch me close for the... way moves. I'm just gonna stand there and come back.
time. Help. I'm very interested in the fact that I'm cold, clean, and all you would take care of my son. I'm going to take some somewhere and then you'll see what I'm going to do. I'm going to just do it. Yeah, I'm going to cut it. Damn, my hair. Are you wet? My hair. In the morning before I go to the shop.
I have to work out. I'm going to start with the one. There it is. I suppose so. I have to work out too many. I have to work out with my doggy. What's the difference? You might still work for a group. Trust me. I'll pay a lot of taxes.
Sorry Fred will need to start paying his own mortgage. I told Judy last night I said I'm not going to be, I mean first supposed to be paying me part of that back at this month but I'm not holding my breath. By the way you didn't pay shit. I did. I didn't pay shit. No. I know I'm just saying. I'm just saying. Yeah but the thing is. You made a sound like you paid his mortgage or something. No. No. I didn't pay his mortgage. But what I'm saying.
if that will start happening. This money is coming out with what you will save in for a long time, something that you really want. That's true. If it's going to continue, then both of us will be paying for it. No, I told Judy, and I told Alina, I said that I got it. Yes.
I saw because I would look at her mortgage account, you know, she wouldn't make my bank account do it or some shit and fuck that. But anyway, so I saw what she owes on her mortgage. She only has like $12,000 in equity. Yeah. And I mean, I don't think that house was gonna look appraised for anything more than it did before. Shit. She didn't even get in the prairie to through the front door. Anyway, so I said, you know what, if she loses that house.
Fine, I'm not helping her fuck it. She can figure it out on her own. Because she's made her choices. She's chosen Fred over the kids. And it's her fucking problem, you know? Honestly, if she loses the house, she loses a few thousand dollars in equity, and she'll have to go get an apartment. And she probably won't be able to afford one big enough for Fred. So maybe it'll be a good thing. All the things is gotta start the president soon.
because right now it came out of your money. You know, you're helping the out of your money that your painstaking can be taken. What did I help you with? Well, don't you periodically help her out with taxes? I don't know how much that's happening. Like, but- No, I forget how much, uh... But she pays it all back. That's a thing. She's like the sole reason for you, that's also a true forget- You know, but, uh, she's also in the verge, always on one of the things that's happening. So, I'm gonna rush on a thousand bucks.
But what I'm saying, I feel really bad for you because it always comes from something you've been saying for years, for something that's up for your dream. And if you... I was going to say I put a lot to what you're credit card too. And I'm repaying. Yeah, I know, I'm just saying. It's not like everybody, I mean, it sounds like you're picking on my family. I'm not picking on the family. I'm not saying that. What's that?
But I mean, you know, no, I'm what I'm trying to say is that when like Judy's paying back I've paid back I'm gonna give you like with text text is I'm gonna give you the charts I've been putting With money on our cotton on our discover and everything so I'm at least they pay back What I'm saying is Fred the president has been sat long time ago When everybody wants to pledge
Fred don't bless them, well he was very clear of language. We're saying that Jennifer's family is expected to take in care of. Oh yeah, I didn't want to tell him what is going to happen if you get her in trouble with her work and she loses her job. Then with one of the kids that you care so much about going to do, he's like, oh I don't know where it should find another job. Oh that's a thing, he sounds exactly like my first husband. But, but, but, but, but I know what I mean.
It's just like it's just talking. But nobody said anything otherwise. And if he says that's what's going to happen. So he's not going to have... Oh, oh, I have a dirty bowl. I don't want to do with it. Can you help me? So what I want is what's going to happen. The expectation was that the person who was going to have a bowl
I'm sure you've made that when your money is gone, we will have to start helping. You know, the Alleen's done, I'm done. There's nobody left. She bombed 100 bucks actually. Well, well, yeah, frankly, they're fucking that. Especially when they found out that he's sad. The friend back. My fucking dad. Everybody's done.
I got it inheritance. I've paramed out. I get it inheritance. When Frank was gone, he's given me his oppressors. His plight-outers.
He's got his gun stuff. I'll probably get a couple things to Yeah, and he needs to work for on great too And I've given lots of things to be proud of but I guess I'm just not good at
the way I behave. And you were asked if he wants to do something. And you can't do it. Would you like to do something? If he thinks he's going to the business, he's going to do something. And you need to start. That's what it is. Just like David did, David, Kramen, the law paring, you need to start doing this. Sure, that's down. I'm going to die. So it's a parent. So I need that.
I need to go check. Oh, on your... No, because honestly... The wrap thingy. You want... you care? I don't know what to put on there, honestly. I'm just going to put some eggs and some... You want beans on there? Okay. Thank you so much for going to the wrap with... Yeah, but no, no. It's not about picking those up on eggs except for a... I'm sure this... I've got that in that case of you.
and she's gonna be okay. Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes. Yeah, because Fred is going to continue with what I mean and Fred is going to continue with Fred. Yeah. I just killed me when she said that. But it's still Fred. He's still in there, you know? Yeah, yeah. I met the motherfucker. He's good. It went, you brought the motherfucker to my mom's house and when I met him, he was in bed with my other sister. That's still Fred. No, it's just it is just...
I think it's largely just nobody's perfect. People do stupid shit, but everybody do stupid shit. Hey. Except you. Yes. You were making that. No, but the first is a lot of people stop doing stupid shit. I call it a way to get it based on one of the time. At some stupid time, he's pushing 50. If he did a straight enough now, that's not going to happen. You see, really pushing 50? How old is he? I thought it was going to be a little...
younger than me. It's a sport. It's a sport. Jennifer's is here in Younger and I am. So she'll be here. Yeah. That's it. Man, it's scrambled eggs scrambled fast. It's a little habit of what time. So, how do you guys figure out how to do some chicken more? Or let's do it slower. AHHHHH!
Oh 52 years old I can't do stupid shit quite as fast as I used to. Well, we'll read to my boss this year he's uh, he, we're the same year then he's 70 four or the, he's just, uh, November 5th, like how? Ah nice. So I did the, uh, did he, does he know Guy Fox? He's the host that, oh yeah. I thought I asked him to give him a stir, so he's gonna give him a stir. Well, I'm not gonna tell you.
from that. But I did spend the evening, I did spend the whole Sunday, stuck in like freezer up, but anyway, if he actually had a birthday, but anyway, but anyway, I feel saying like, it would tell you to turn 50 couple of months before me.
like how those of the field my mind birthdays coming up. This is like I'm still gonna do stupid stuff just slower. Ha ha ha ha ha. That wasn't your turn, Russian. But it's all from now. Sounds about right. That's it. That's it. Yoooo!
No! Not really. He was just, we crawled into her bed to wake her up, but it was really fucking weird. I bet it was really weird for her too. Some black dude she had and that was in her bed when she woke up. Now maybe it was normal for her, I don't know.
How do you do this with his saddles? His saddles.
Okay, so, yeah, so, yeah, it's plastic not cheers, cheers, cheers. Da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da. Okay, so, yeah, so, yeah. Okay, so, yeah.
I'm not going to be wrong, I'll try to get them there one the next one.
I'm going to do it for you. I'm going to do it for you. I'm going to do it for you. I'm going to do this.
Okay, I need to take this off. I'll give this a two-oblin data. Oh no, I can't use this for two-oblin, so I'll just use this.
Is that blowing up everywhere?
I'm going to do a little taste test here.
Yeah. Wow. You already want spring break? I'm just kidding. I don't know.
I'm not sure. I have to look it up.
What? Oh, I don't know. I don't know if your mom has time or not. I don't know. But yeah, we'll do it.
but I'm not sure if we'll do it all together or not. I'm game. You wanna do it early afternoon because I'm making some breakfast burritos right now. That will do, have like a one or there, assuming they're open, let me check their hours, but I think that'll work.
I just throw that shit everywhere. Okay, what's next? Beans.
nd engineer
Not right now? Alright. Mama gets a double. How about should the one and a half? I can make you another one later. There's actually eggs.
...
I'm sorry, there's my bag. Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, it's really bad.
Oh God. I'm going to put the water in the pot. I'm going to put the water in the pot.
All right, we've got knackens. Oh! Peter Mollister.
Here you go. You want this done here or not? Here is your numb and your neat drum. I'm going to go into my hole and you mine. Now I'm going to go in my hole.
I'm going to put it in here. I'm going to put it in here. I'm going to put it in here.
Oh, what? I didn't even ask to open that again. Poo, over. Alright, I'll rob that.
Go. I don't know.
Oh What
Cute.
흥, 흥, 봐봐
Oh, okay, well fucking judge me, would I, would you?
I'm just moving on. Oh! BEEP BEEP BEEP There it is. Cleared. Nice.
How you just want to be like it's all heading judging out there's
Oh
I You could do that.
If you need anything on Amazon or something, there's a lot discounted. I only bought the pack of underwear that I needed and two bras. $14 for bras. But it's better than $35. Well, that's expensive. $14. $14? Yeah. $14 this day is no. That's cheap. That's cheap.
That's what I'm saying, but it's like bras were always I mean how many kids do you have? Exactly so I bought two brother and bras are 14 dollars because they're because regular crisis 23 So I was waiting for it like I saw it before it dropped and I was like I'm waiting Like
I was jealous you have so many underwears. So you don't have to wash them all the time. I rocked out of underwear all the time. Hmm. You want to keep fighting my dirty underwear in your pile? No. I just turned them inside out and then... I'll leave you with that.
Yeah, there were a lot of discounts today. Some reasons. Oh, good. Yeah. I don't think I need anything. I hate to say it, but I don't think I need anything. Yeah.
1.5% 1.5% 1.5%
1.5% 1.5% 1.5% 1.5%